<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>The Heretic</title>
		<link>http://theheretic.me</link>
		<atom:link href="http://theheretic.me/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		<description>An opinionated Newsletter by Pascal Finette</description>
		<pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2013 17:57:07 +0700</pubDate>
		<lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2013 17:57:07 +0700</lastBuildDate>
		
			<item>
				<title>A Bad Man, Phnom Penh</title>
				<link>http://theheretic.me/2013/11/12/phnompenh-madman</link>
				<pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2013 15:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<author>hello@theheretic.me (Pascal Finette)</author>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://theheretic.me/2013/11/12/phnompenh-madman</guid>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/posts/2013-11-10-brussels-driss.png&quot; alt=&quot;Madman in Phnom Penh&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Before we get started, nobody panic. I gave the full account of the following to five people I would trust with my life before I finally went to sleep. I am safe.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the words of my wise friend, Jessica Heinzleman, &quot;Welcome to international work.  It is fraught with weirdos, wackos and some scary individuals.&quot; I&#39;ve hit my halfway point of this journey, six weeks down, six more weeks to go and I&#39;m just now running into someone fitting her description. We&#39;ll omit his name and the specific location and any other identifying details. Suffice to say, a boisterous asshole sidled up to the bar, inquiring in an Eastern bloc accent seasoned with five decades of tobacco &quot;Are you one of those Americans who would be angry if I smoked.&quot; I replied &quot;Sit down, have a cigarette and tell me a story.&quot; This isn&#39;t the first time the voice in my head that gleefully shrieks &quot;this is going to be &lt;strong&gt;the best story&lt;/strong&gt;&quot; has gotten me in a scrape. We started off with him declaring that I had the best short haircut on a woman he&#39;d seen in twenty years. If you can conjure this image, this man&#39;s man who later showed me his permit to carry a glock, his lined face giggling as he proclaimed French men to be the best hairdressers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What I hoped would be a charming asshole turned out to be a nasty combination of bully and bigot. Darkness descended with the second cocktail. He bragged that in his youth he&#39;d killed people for fun. I asked what he does now for fun. &quot;It&#39;s boring now.&quot; In a calm tone he reassured me that he &quot;wouldn&#39;t keep you for myself. I&#39;d sell you.&quot; Oh wow, this is good information for me to know. Than didn&#39;t scare me visibly, so then he moved onto threatening to revoke my visa, effective immediately. Fantastic. &quot;That&#39;s fine, I&#39;m happy to go back home.&quot; By this point, I was desperate for an exit path. When he went to the bathroom, one of the staff came over and told me he was a bad man and asked what I wanted to do. I&#39;ve never been more impatient for a credit card to process. They ushered me out the side door into a waiting motorcycle taxi. I rode back to my apartment with head ducked below the seat.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&#39;m reassured that if he was a REALLY bad man, they would&#39;ve put me in a car and taken me to safety. Nobody wants the international PR a disappeared American would bring. There is a US Consulate right in the middle of town.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another day, another story, another lesson. Till the next one, take care my friends.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Blessing, Phnom Penh</title>
				<link>http://theheretic.me/2013/10/19/phnompenh-blessing</link>
				<pubDate>Sat, 19 Oct 2013 15:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<author>hello@theheretic.me (Pascal Finette)</author>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://theheretic.me/2013/10/19/phnompenh-blessing</guid>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/posts/2013-10-19-phnompenh-blessing.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;The Blessing came for me&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Whatever you do – aim for emotion. Make people passionately love you, your product or your company. And understand that when some people love you, others will hate you.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Driss, Brussels</title>
				<link>http://theheretic.me/2013/10/06/brussels-driss</link>
				<pubDate>Sun, 06 Oct 2013 15:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<author>hello@theheretic.me (Pascal Finette)</author>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://theheretic.me/2013/10/06/brussels-driss</guid>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/posts/2013-11-10-brussels-driss.png&quot; alt=&quot;Driss in Brussels&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Whatever you do – aim for emotion. Make people passionately love you, your product or your company. And understand that when some people love you, others will hate you.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>