<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>The Heretic</title>
		<link>http://theheretic.me</link>
		<atom:link href="http://theheretic.me/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		<description>An opinionated Newsletter by Pascal Finette</description>
		<pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2013 17:45:52 +0700</pubDate>
		<lastBuildDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2013 17:45:52 +0700</lastBuildDate>
		
			<item>
				<title>Hate Or Love</title>
				<link>http://theheretic.me/2013/11/05/hate-or-love</link>
				<pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2013 15:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<author>hello@theheretic.me (Pascal Finette)</author>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://theheretic.me/2013/11/05/hate-or-love</guid>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Whatever you do – aim for emotion. Make people passionately love you, your product or your company. And understand that when some people love you, others will hate you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The worst possible state is mediocrity – as it&#39;s boring and exhausting.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Too often do I see entrepreneurs who don&#39;t want to offend anyone and thus end up in a sea of blandness. Their products don&#39;t excite, their statements are conformist and in an attempt to appeal to the &quot;broad masses&quot; they loose their edge.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Have an opinion and voice it. Have an edge. We don&#39;t need any more mediocrity in our lives. All the other guys are already taking care of that.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Choose Your Perspective</title>
				<link>http://theheretic.me/2013/11/04/choose-your-perspective</link>
				<pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2013 16:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<author>hello@theheretic.me (Pascal Finette)</author>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://theheretic.me/2013/11/04/choose-your-perspective</guid>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;I spent the last three days at the Coaches Institute (CTI) as part of the training I am doing. This weekend we spent time on perspectives – the notion that you can&#39;t help it but see the world through the filter of our chosen perspective.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We talked about this earlier: There is a fundamental difference in the sentence &quot;I don&#39;t have time&quot; and &quot;It is not a priority for me&quot;. Same underlying truth – different outcomes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The thing you need to burn into your memory is: You are at choice. Always. You might not be able to change the circumstances – but you surely can change your perspective.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Once you have internalized this – you will not be able to go back to your old self and allow yourself to be a victim of the circumstances. You are truly the master of your own destiny.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Godspeed fellow Heretics.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Lucky Or Smart</title>
				<link>http://theheretic.me/2013/10/31/lucky-or-smart</link>
				<pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2013 09:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<author>hello@theheretic.me (Pascal Finette)</author>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://theheretic.me/2013/10/31/lucky-or-smart</guid>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;We talk a lot about rainmaking here at The Heretic HQ – Heretics share a believe that we are the masters of your own destiny, that we shape the outcomes we want and that the future is uncertain (which we celebrate as a good thing).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And yet – there is something important to understand:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You have to be smart enough to realize when you&#39;re lucky.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When luck strikes you need to be able to recognize it, have the chutzpah to follow the lead and make it happen. Trust me – I have missed so many amazing opportunities by not recognizing when luck struck me; it&#39;s not even funny.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With that being said I often get asked: When do you know that luck is about to strike?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I thought about this a lot and the best I can offer you is: &lt;strong&gt;Trust your gut and follow your heart.&lt;/strong&gt; Every single time luck was about to hit me and I failed to act upon it, I knew deep down that I should take the opportunity.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>On Empathy (or Why Loving Someone Is Easy)</title>
				<link>http://theheretic.me/2013/10/30/on-empathy</link>
				<pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2013 14:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<author>hello@theheretic.me (Pascal Finette)</author>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://theheretic.me/2013/10/30/on-empathy</guid>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;We talked about empathy quite a bit here at The Heretic. You need deep customer empathy to build products your customers not only want but desire and love. You should also operate from a place of empathy when dealing with your cofounders and employees.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yesterday, at a leadership workshop, someone asked me how you deal with people who are &quot;hard to deal with&quot;. We all know these people in our lives - we dread interactions with them, we have all sorts of preconceived notions about them and in general they make our lives miserable. For a lot of us the emotional &quot;go-to-place&quot; is confrontational – which makes things only worse (for both sides). When these people are only a short part of an interaction this might be fine (though still not pleasant), when they are partners, coworkers or employees we find ourselves in a world of hurt.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A few weeks ago, at a coaching seminar I attended, the seminar leader said something very profound which changed my view of this situation – and in turn changed my whole outlook:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&quot;It&#39;s easy for me to love you. And that doesn&#39;t mean that I like you.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Humans are hardwired to love other members of our species. It&#39;s a survival instinct. Coming from a place of love (and thus empathy) for someone is easy – as long as you don&#39;t confuse love with liking: I can dearly love you and thus have deep empathy for you without liking you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Try it out. It will make your life much easier, your interactions richer &amp;amp; better and make you a much better leader.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>A Personal Update</title>
				<link>http://theheretic.me/2013/10/29/a-personal-update</link>
				<pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2013 10:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<author>hello@theheretic.me (Pascal Finette)</author>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://theheretic.me/2013/10/29/a-personal-update</guid>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Just want to share this with my Heretic tribe – Yesterday I sent the following email to my dear colleagues at Mozilla:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Subject: So Long, and Thanks for All the Fish // A Personal Update&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dear Friends,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After five wonderful years at &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.mozilla.org/en-US/firefox/video/?video=brand&quot;&gt;Mozilla&lt;/a&gt; the time has come for me to leave the &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=4Q7FTjhvZ7Y&quot;&gt;mothership&lt;/a&gt;, follow my calling and &lt;a href=&quot;http://zeega.com/150647&quot;&gt;dance in the moment&lt;/a&gt; by combining my passions for entrepreneurship, technology and global impact.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It has been an incredible time, a great adventure and an unforgettable journey. From the bottom of my heart I want to thank all of you for making, keeping and continuously evolving Mozilla – a truly &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.mozilla.org/en-US/firefox/video/?video=whatismozilla&quot;&gt;unique place&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am eternally grateful to have had the chance to work with and more importantly learn from some of the most inspiring, most passionate and smartest people in the industry, including the original Labs team (&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_T84_kZeoLY&quot;&gt;Anant&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;http://vimeo.com/2604372&quot;&gt;Atul&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;http://vimeo.com/5483375&quot;&gt;Aza&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=gC0USgAawpg&quot;&gt;Ben A&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;http://vimeo.com/3195079&quot;&gt;Ben G and Dion A&lt;/a&gt; (they only come in a pair), &lt;a href=&quot;http://vimeo.com/27177893&quot;&gt;Brian&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;http://vimeo.com/2569344&quot;&gt;Dan M&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.directorypatent.com/US/07739604.html&quot;&gt;Dan W&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.webmonkey.com/2011/04/awesomebar-hd-packs-more-awesomeness-into-firefox/&quot;&gt;Ed&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;http://vimeo.com/12373225&quot;&gt;Jinghua&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.flickr.com/photos/gen/4776811766/in/photostream/&quot;&gt;Joe&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;http://vimeo.com/2974320&quot;&gt;Jono&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=sM_xG3Hl0_w&quot;&gt;Kevin&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=iBFVrmyald4&quot;&gt;Lloyd&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;http://vimeo.com/12092555&quot;&gt;Mike&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;http://vimeo.com/2756134&quot;&gt;Myk&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=lv96VuMQvj0&quot;&gt;Ragavan&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.flickr.com/photos/nitot/4786445371/in/photosof-mart3ll/&quot;&gt;Sean&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;http://vimeo.com/2832032&quot;&gt;Suneel&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;http://tobyelliott.wordpress.com/&quot;&gt;Toby&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7Xc2lQdGFQ0&quot;&gt;Zandr&lt;/a&gt;), the incredible WebFWD crew (&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=IO8jAUUHD90&quot;&gt;Diane&lt;/a&gt; &amp;amp; &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=f6pu8nY7zBY&quot;&gt;Didem&lt;/a&gt;), the &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=KIFvKVJ6vk4&quot;&gt;Identity&lt;/a&gt; gang (sorry guys - you&#39;re too many to list) and the awesome &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Mh-TxzPaNzI&quot;&gt;#MozSummit&lt;/a&gt; crew (you know who you are! #amazing #hashtag #&amp;lt;3).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Thank you. You make this place special.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In addition to working with these wicked smart people I must have won the boss-lottery – having had four of the most amazing people as my bosses: &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=jgGPJAf_rlQ&quot;&gt;Chris&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;http://wordpress.tv/2009/07/08/john-lilly-mozilla/&quot;&gt;John&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.viddler.com/v/3ecee4e1&quot;&gt;Todd&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=fjHEfhVnIxo&quot;&gt;Mitchell&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Thank you. You believed in me and taught me so, so much.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Not to forget my fellow &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=wPOgvzVOQig&quot;&gt;LEADers&lt;/a&gt; from &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=5NP8y63Ms4o&quot;&gt;cohort&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=04854XqcfCY&quot;&gt;one&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;http://ideatribe.com/tribe/athena.htm&quot;&gt;Athena&lt;/a&gt; &amp;amp; &lt;a href=&quot;http://ideatribe.com/tribe/kate.htm&quot;&gt;Kate&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;I love you guys! You made me grow.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And it&#39;s not only the people I worked with directly – it&#39;s all of you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You are just incredible!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And yet – as so often in life: Good things have come to an end eventually. So let me leave you with a quote from &lt;a href=&quot;http://zeega.com/152820&quot;&gt;Alan Watts&lt;/a&gt; – may it serve you well on your journey:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&quot;The only way to make sense out of change is to plunge into it, move with it and join the dance.&quot;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;So Long, and Thanks for All the Fish!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stay in touch! &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:p@finette.com&quot;&gt;p@finette.com&lt;/a&gt; // &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/pfinette&quot;&gt;Facebook&lt;/a&gt; // &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.linkedin.com/in/pfinette&quot;&gt;LinkedIn&lt;/a&gt; // &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/pfinette&quot;&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt; // &lt;a href=&quot;http://finette.com/&quot;&gt;Homepage&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Oh - and as someone much wiser than I said before: “&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=JRL5Z1k60tg&quot;&gt;Farewell, but not goodbye!&lt;/a&gt;” I am working with Mitchell and others on very concrete ways to &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.mozilla.org/en-US/contribute/&quot;&gt;stay involved&lt;/a&gt;. More on that soon.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With deep admiration,
&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=u8h8ca5zn5Y&quot;&gt;Pascal&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;P.S. I will stay around for a tiny bit longer - my last day in the office will be Thursday, Oct 31st when I will leave for a short trip during which I will be available on email and phone. Officially my last day will be Friday, November 8th.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;P.P.S. If the suspension is about to kill you and you just need to know what I will be doing next… &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=dQw4w9WgXcQ&quot;&gt;This&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Don&#39;t Try To Predict The Future</title>
				<link>http://theheretic.me/2013/10/28/dont-try-to-predict-the-future</link>
				<pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2013 10:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<author>hello@theheretic.me (Pascal Finette)</author>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://theheretic.me/2013/10/28/dont-try-to-predict-the-future</guid>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;I recently read in a research paper on entrepreneurship:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&quot;To the extend that we can control the future, we do not need to predict it.&quot;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is a profound statement – especially when you take into account that the best entrepreneurs usually come from a position of not believing that the future is somewhere &quot;out there&quot; to be discovered, but that it gets created through their very strategies and actions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Most entrepreneurs I know prefer to be in unpredictable markets; markets that can be shaped by their own decisions and actions – as opposed to compete in predictable (often more mature) markets where they face the uphill battle of fighting with people who might be smarter and better resourced.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Make no mistake: As an entrepreneur you are in the business of creating the future.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;P.S. Apologies for the slightly off-schedule postings lately. A lot going on here. More on this soon…&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>First Time CEOs</title>
				<link>http://theheretic.me/2013/10/25/first-time-ceos</link>
				<pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2013 11:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<author>hello@theheretic.me (Pascal Finette)</author>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://theheretic.me/2013/10/25/first-time-ceos</guid>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;The last two days I had the privilege to support a leadership development program here at Mozilla. It&#39;s an incredible gift to work with people on their personal development and see them transform over the course of two short days. Then, this morning, I had the pleasure of talking with one of our fellow Heretics about her personal journey as an early startup employee.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The scene which played out for her is one which is typical for startups: The founder is a first-time CEO. In his efforts to do the right thing he micromanages her, stifles her creativity &amp;amp; abilities and overall just creates tension.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Trust me: I&#39;ve been there myself. Being a first time CEO is incredibly hard. I was in a constant state of anxiousness, insecurity and fear. I felt like someone threw me into the deep end of the pool and I just hadn&#39;t learned to swim yet. I was scared shitless. Everything was new. A lot of things didn&#39;t make sense anymore. I didn&#39;t have any patterns to rely on.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Gladly I had amazing mentors who helped me, told me the hard truths and showed me the way. And the one thing I learned is: Your sole responsibility as a CEO is to formulate the vision, set the strategic direction, hire the right people, express intent and then get the hell out of your people&#39;s way. Once they are in motion your sole role is to support them and make sure that they follow the broad path lined out by the vision and strategy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Spend the next 10 minutes watching this – it will teach you more about leadership than a two-year MBA course:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;640&quot; height=&quot;480&quot; src=&quot;//www.youtube.com/embed/OqmdLcyES_Q?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

</description>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>The Right Stuff</title>
				<link>http://theheretic.me/2013/10/22/the-right-stuff</link>
				<pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2013 12:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<author>hello@theheretic.me (Pascal Finette)</author>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://theheretic.me/2013/10/22/the-right-stuff</guid>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Every entrepreneur starts out with three things. These three things are the essence of every entrepreneur. Understanding, appreciating, cultivating and leveraging these three things make or break an entrepreneur.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Every entrepreneur begins with three categories of means:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Who they are&lt;/strong&gt; – their traits, tastes and abilities.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What they know&lt;/strong&gt; – their education, training, expertise and experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Whom they know&lt;/strong&gt; – their social and professional network.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Everything the entrepreneur creates is based on these means.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;This is the right stuff.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ask yourself: Who are you? What do you know? Whom do you know? Now – what can you create with this?&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Whom Are You Building For?</title>
				<link>http://theheretic.me/2013/10/21/whom-are-you-building-for</link>
				<pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2013 12:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<author>hello@theheretic.me (Pascal Finette)</author>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://theheretic.me/2013/10/21/whom-are-you-building-for</guid>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&quot;We&#39;ve finally built the product that we&#39;d want to use.&quot;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Those were the exact words a technical cofounder recently used to describe his product to his team. He couldn&#39;t be more wrong…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Most startups build products for people other than themselves. The founders might be part of the demographic but more often than not they are not THE demographic. Or the full spectrum of the demography. There are exceptions of course – the team of hackers which builds tools for developers. But even the car mechanic who builds the &quot;perfect&quot; car mechanics software represents only one very specific fraction of the market.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You have to build your product for your customers. At least if you want to do this as a business. By all means – make sure you love your product as well. But never forget the customer.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Use Chopsticks</title>
				<link>http://theheretic.me/2013/10/18/use-chopsticks</link>
				<pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2013 15:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<author>hello@theheretic.me (Pascal Finette)</author>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://theheretic.me/2013/10/18/use-chopsticks</guid>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;The following guest post is from a good friend and fellow Heretic &lt;a href=&quot;http://matejnovak.com/&quot;&gt;Matej Novak&lt;/a&gt;, a copywriter with a deep passion for language and branding.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was born in 1977 in what was then communist Czechoslovakia. We ate with knives and forks. Sometimes spoons. Going out to dinner was something special, an occasion, and eating with chopsticks made it even more so. It presented a challenge, but also created memories and an opportunity to learn.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Your background may be different, so this exact metaphor may not work for you. But it&#39;s not really about chopsticks. It&#39;s not even about food. It&#39;s about changing your routine from time to time, trying new things and appreciating the world and your life in a new way.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1) Slow down&lt;/strong&gt;
Small bites. One piece a time. Chew. It&#39;s not always just about the destination. The process and journey are just as important — sometimes more. Take the time to notice. Important learning happens along the way.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2) Make it special&lt;/strong&gt;
Turn something ordinary into an occasion. Involve friends and family. Celebrate, even the little things (especially the little things). Don&#39;t wait for these situations to present themselves. Create them yourself.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3) Turn it into a ritual&lt;/strong&gt;
Ritual and ceremony are incredibly powerful. How many times have you gone to sleep in your life? How many of those do you remember? Find ways to change habits. Perform routine tasks in new ways.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&#39;s amazing how easily you can incorporate these things into your life. They don&#39;t take a lot of time or effort, even if it may feel that way at first. Try them one at a time. Combine them. You don&#39;t have to do all (or even any) of them every day, but when you do, it can be very rewarding.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When I think back to some of my favorite experiences, the ones that really stand out in my mind, the ones I most wish I could go back and relive, they all have at least a couple of these things in common.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>